let me drag you back to programming first. Like what?
Three, maybe 3 to 5 programming languages Should people learn, Do you think?
Like, if you look at yourself, what did you get the most out of
from learning?
Well, so
everybody should learn. See an assembly. We'll start with those two.
Assembly.
Yeah, If you can't coding assembly, you don't know what the computer's doing.
You don't understand. Like
you want to be great assembly, but you have to code in it.
And then like,
you have to appreciate assembly in order to
appreciate all the great things see gets you.
And then you have to code and see in order
to appreciate all the great things by that gets you.
So obviously, assembly seeing python will start with those three
the memory allocation of sea and the
the fact that s o somebody gives you a sense of just how many loves abstraction
you get to work on in modern day. Yeah. Graft.
Hollering for assignment, register signed and compilers.
Yeah, you know,
you gotta do you know the companion computer
only has a certain number of registered.
You can have all the variables you want to see function.
You know, you get to start your
intuition about compilation
like
Kampala gets you.
What else?
Well, then there's then there's kind of ah,
so those are all very imperative for languages.
Then there's two other paradigms for programming
that everybody should be familiar with.
I'm one of dysfunctional.
You should learn Haskell and take that all the way through.
Learn a language with dependent types like cock
learn that whole space like the very pl theory Heavy languages
and has caused your favourite functional.
But is that the go to?
Yeah, I'm not. I'm not a great Haskell programmer. Welcome, pilot Haskell ones.
There's another paradigm, and actually,
there's one more paradigm l'd even talk about after that that I
never used to talk about when I would think about this.
But the next paradigm has learned barrel
of HDL
off.
Understand this idea of all of the instructions executed once
you have a blocking vara log and I right
stuff in it, it's not sequential.
They all execute it once
on them, like things like that. That's a hard works
to be.
So I guess assembly doesn't quite get you that somebody's more about compilation
and very log is more about the hardware,
like giving us. That's what actually is the hardware is doing
assembly. See, python are straight like that. They sit right on top of each other.
In fact, see is
well,
it's kind of coded and say But you could imagine the first sea was coated in assembly
line is actually coated in C.
S. O. You know, you can straight up. Go on that.
God,
I'm in viral. I give a zb. Brilliant.
Okay, and then I think there's another one. Now
everyone's Carpathia costed programming to point out
which is learn
a
I'm never going.
Don't learn tensorflow
pytorch.
So, machine learning.
We gotta come up with a better term, then programming to 0.0. R.
But yeah, it's a programming language.
I wonder if it could be formalise a little bit better,
which we feel like we're in the early days.
What? That actually entails
data driven programming
data driven programming. Yeah,
but so fundamentally different as a paradigm than the others.
Like it almost requires a different skill set.
But you think yeah,
implied towards first tensorflow pytorch wins.
It is the fourth
time. It's the fourth paradigm that I've kind of seen
there's like this, you know?
Imperative. Functional
hardware. I don't know a better word for it,
and then the mail.